Finding Aid for Personnel Office (University of Michigan) Records, 1940-1999
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Topical Files of Assistant to the Vice President for Academic Affairs
  - Colleen Dolan-Greene, 1986-1993
    - Minority Affairs, Office of, 1987-1989 (Box 9)
    - Misconduct, Academic, 1985 (Box 9)
    - Molecular Genetics, Center for
      - General, 1985-1986 (Box 9)
      - Staff and Faculty Evaluations, 1985 (Box 31)
    - Monthly Personnel Reports and Comparisons
      - General, 1980-1992; 9 folders (Box 9)
      - Automation and Information Technology, 1988-1989 (Box 9)
      - Administrative Services Personnel Office (ASPO) Service Center, 1988-1989 (Box 10)
      - Dearborn Service Center, 1988-1989 (Box 10)
      - Faculty and Staff Statistics, Office of, 1988-1989 (Box 10)
      - Flint Service Center, 1988-1989 (Box 10)
      - Human Resource Development, 1988-1989 (Box 10)
      - Medical Campus Human Resources Department, 1988-1990 (Box 10)
      - Medical Center, 1988-1989 (Box 10)
      - Schools, Colleges, Institutes and Libraries (SCIL) Service Center, 1988-1989 (Box 10)
      - Six Month and Year End Comparisons, 1988-1989 (Box 10)
      - Staff Benefits, 1988-1989 (Box 10)
      - Staff and Union Relations, 1988-1989 (Box 10)
      - Tuition Refund Statistics, 1988-1989 (Box 10)
      - University Compensation, 1988-1989 (Box 10)
    - Mortgage Assistance
      - General, 1983-1984 (Box 10)
      - Loan Requests, 1984 (Box 31)
    - Motor Vehicle Operators, 1988 (Box 10)
    - Non Discrimination Efforts
      - General, 1986-1988 (Box 11)
      - Employment Benefits, 1989-1990 (Box 11)
    - Office Move, 1986 (Box 11)
    - Priority Projects, 1988 (Box 11)
    - Promotions
      - General, 1980-1993; 7 folders (Box 11)
      - Faculty and Staff Evaluations, 1980-1984; 4 folders (Box 31)
    - Salary
      - Averages, 1985-1986 (Box 11)
      - Averages by Job Family, 1986-1987 (Box 11)
      - Comparison Data, 1983-1984 (Box 11)
      - Comparative Instructional Salary Data, 1985-1989; 4 folders (Box 11)
      - Data by Discipline, 1985 (Box 11)
      - Equity
        - General, 1971-1989 (Box 11)
        - Compensation Requests, 1988 (Box 31)
          [PR RESTRICTED until July 1 2018 ]
      - Policy, 1967-1986 (Box 11)
      - Salary and Benefit Program Recommendations, Ann Arbor General Fund, 1987-1988 (Box 11)
    - Salary Grade Change Recommendations, 1983-1989 (Box 11)
    - Schools, Colleges, Institutes and Libraries (SCIL), 1986-1989 (Box 11)
    - Secretary Classifications Review, 1969-1970 (Box 11)
    - Senate Advisory Committee on University Affairs (SACUA) Issues, 1982-1990 (Box 11)
    - Staff Benefits Committee
      - General, 1986-1991; 10 folders (Box 11)
      - Calvert Group Investment, 1986-1988 (Box 11)
      - Complaints and Grievances, 1987 (Box 31)
      - Evaluation, 1990 (Box 31)
        [PR RESTRICTED until July 1 2020 ]
      - Health Care and Retirement, 1986-1987 (Box 11)
      - Investments and Retirement, 1989-1990 (Box 11)
    - Staff Directory, 1981-1984; 2 folders (Box 11)
    - Statistical Data Form, 1985 (Box 11)
    - Teaching Assistants and Class Size, 1988-1989; 2 folders (Box 11)
    - Tenure (Box 12)
      - Accumulation of Service, 1985-1993 (Box 12)
      - "Chronology of Tenure Policy 1974-1981 / Medical School De Facto Tenure," 1981 (Box 12)
      - Discussion Booklet, 1969-1973 (Box 12)
      - Issues, 1980-1987
        - General, 1980-1992; 7 folders (Box 12)
        - Faculty and Staff Evaluations, 1980 (Box 31)
      - Probationary Issues, 1974-1989 (Box 12)
      - Tenure Liaison Committee, 1982-1987; 2 folders (Box 12)
    - Unions and Union Negotiations
      - American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees (AFSCME)
        - Collective Bargaining, 1983-1984; 3 folders (Box 12)
        - Negotiations, 1980-1986; 3 folders (Box 12)
      - Campus Staff and Union Reports, 1977 (Box 12)
      - International Union of Operating Engineers (IUOE)
        - General, 1981; 2 folders (Box 12)
        - Bargaining, 1984 (Box 12)
      - Trades
        - General, 1981; 2 folders (Box 13)
        - Agreement, 1986-1988 (Box 13)
        - Bargaining, 1984 (Box 13)
        - Negotiations, 1981-1986; 2 folders (Box 13)
    - University Hospital
      - House Officers Association (HOA), 1989 (Box 13)
      - Michigan Nurses Association (MNA), 1986-1989 (Box 13)
      - Nursing Staff, 1989 (Box 13)
    - Vice President for Academic Affairs, 1980-1981 (Box 13)
    - Vice President for Research, 1983-1989 (Box 13)
    - Staff, 1987-1991
      - Vice Provost for Information Technology, 1984-1989 (Box 13)
    - Visitors, 1988-1989 (Box 13)
- Personnel Data Systems (PDS) Files
  The Personnel Data Systems (PDS) Files series (1.5 linear ft.) documents Personnel Data Systems, a group responsible for incorporating data processing technologies into the system that responds to data-based information survey requests. The series consists of two subseries: a Chronological File running from 1969 to 1984, and a Topical File.
  - Chronological Files
    - (Management Information System Study), 1969 (Box 13)
    - 1975 (Box 13)
    - (re: research change of identification away from social security number for security), 1976; 2 folders (Box 13)
    - (new employee data forms), 1977 (Box 13)
    - 1978, 2 folders (Box 14)
    - 1979 (Box 14)
    - 1980-1984 (Box 14)
  - Topical Files
    - Computer File Revision, 1970-1971 (Box 14)
    - Data Element Dictionary Task Force, 1973 (Box 14)
    - Expense Class Code, 1971-1978 (Box 14)
    - Human Resource Planning Project, 1973-1975 (Box 14)
    - New Forms, 1975-1978 (Box 14)
    - Personnel Information System, 1967-1968 (Box 14)
    - Schedule Six Code, 1970-1971 (Box 14)
    - Security Task Force, 1974-1976; 5 folders (Box 14)
    - Supervisory Group, 1972-1981 (Box 14)
    - Systems and Procedures, 1968-1980; 4 folders (Box 14)
    - Task Force, 1972-1977 (Box 14)
- Graduate Student Assistants (GSA)/Graduate Employees Organization (GEO) Files
  The Graduate Student Assistants (GSA)/Graduate Employees Organization (GEO) Files (8 linear ft.) series dates from 1949 to 1985 (primarily 1974 to 1980). The records deal with the Personnel Office's relationship with GEO and, to a limited extent, earlier attempts to unionize graduate student assistants. The material has been arranged into three sub series. The Chronological Files measure seven feet and makes up the bulk of the records. It is supplemented by a second sub series, Miscellaneous Material and a third sub series, Arbitration/Grievances.
  - Chronological Files (Box 15)
    - 1949-1950, undated (Box 15)
    - 1970, 3 folders (Box 15)
    - 1971-1973
      - Proposed Graduate Student Program (Box 15)
    - 1973-1974
      - Remuneration Schedule (Box 15)
    - 1974
      - General (Box 15)
      - Bargaining Data (Box 15)
      - Grievance Procedures (Box 15)
      - Negotiations, 2 folders (Box 15)
      - Negotiator's Reference File, 6 folders (Box 16)
      - Questionnaire (Box 16)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 17)
      - Advisory Committee (Box 17)
      - Data (Box 17)
      - Negotiations, 6 folders (Box 17)
      - Survey (Box 17)
    - 1975
      - General (Box 17)
      - Agreement, March 13, 1975 (Box 17)
    - 1975-1976
      - Affirmative Action Progress Report (Box 17)
      - Negotiations, 3 folders
        - Folders 1-2 (Box 17)
        - Folder 3 (Box 18)
      - Programs, Notices, Correspondence, etc. (Box 18)
      - Survey (Box 18)
    - 1976
      - Negotiations, 9 folders (Box 18)
      - Proposals (Box 18)
      - Communications (Box 19)
      - Contract, 26 folders (Box 19)
        (arranged by article)
    - 1976-1977
      - Contract, 26 folders (Box 19)
        (arranged by article / memo of understanding)
      - Contract Modifications (Box 19)
      - Advisory Committee (Box 19)
      - Programs, Notices, Correspondence, etc. (Box 19)
    - 1977
      - General (Box 19)
      - Challenges to GSA's as Employees (Box 20)
    - 1977-1978, 3 folders (Box 20)
    - 1978
      - Hearing Notices (Box 20)
    - 1979, 2 folders (Box 20)
    - 1979-1980
      - General, 2 folders (Box 20)
      - Survey, 2 folders (Box 20)
    - 1980-1981 (includes 1979-1980), 4 folders (Box 21)
    - 1981
      - Agreement, November 23, 1981 (Box 21)
      - 1981-1982 (Box 21)
    - 1982
      - General (Box 21)
      - Contract (Box 21)
    - 1982-1983
      - General (Box 21)
      - Negotiations, 2 folders (Box 21)
    - 1983
      - Agreement, December 12, 1983 (Box 21)
    - 1984
      - General (Box 21)
      - Tuition Waiver Tax problem (Box 21)
    - 1985
      - General (Box 21)
      - Negotiations (Box 21)
      - Agreement, April 29, 1985 (Box 21)
    - Miscellaneous Files
      - Program, 1974-1976 (Box 21)
      - GEO Documents, 1974-1977 (Box 21)
    - 1990-1991
      - Appointment Information, 1991 (Box 34)
      - Contract, 1991; 2 folders (Box 34)
      - Grievances
        - General, 1991 (Box 34)
        - Math Department, 1991 (Box 34)
        - Math and Psychology Departments, 1991 (Box 34)
      - Infrastructure Fee, 1991 (Box 34)
      - Mediation
        - 4/3/1991 (Box 35)
        - 4/12/1991 (Box 35)
        - 4/15/1991 (Box 35)
        - 4/18/1991 (Box 35)
        - 8/8/1991 (Box 35)
        - General (Box 35)
      - Memorandum to Academic Community, 1991 (Box 35)
      - Negotiations
        - Advisory Committee, 1991; 2 folders (Box 35)
        - Background, 1991 (Box 35)
        - Correspondence, 1991 (Box 35)
        - Economic Background, 1991 (Box 35)
        - GEO Communication, 1991 (Box 35)
        - General, 1990-1991; 4 folders (Box 35)
        - Notes, 1991 (Box 35)
        - Proposals, 1991 (Box 35)
        - Tentative Agreements, 1991 (Box 35)
        - University Team, 1991 (Box 35)
      - Strike Effect, 1991 (Box 35)
      - Verification of Effort Form, 1991 (Box 35)
  - GEO Negotiation Newsletter, 1975-1976 (Box 22)
    (Published by Personnel Office to explain the university's bargaining position)
    - Student Assistantship Program, 1973-1980 (Box 22)
  - Arbitration/Grievances, 1974-1978; 61 folders (Box 22)
- Memoranda to Deans, Directors, and Department Heads, 1963-1989
  Memoranda to Deans, Directors, and Department Heads (1 linear ft.), 1963-1989, principally from the office of the Assistant Vice President for Academic Affairs/Faculty Personnel Administration, are arranged chronologically by calendar year. The memos dictate university-wide personnel matters and are directed at those capable of disseminating their contents to large numbers of employees. They deal with a variety of policy and procedural issues including appointment, promotion, and compensation of faculty and graduate assistants.
  - 1963-1989, 16 folders (Box 23)
- Administrative Files, 1963-1994
  Administrative Files were received in several accessions, each of which is described as a separate, chronologically bounded subseries. The inclusive dates of the subseries overlap and topics and the same topics maybe included in more than one subseries.
  - 1980-1992
    Administrative Files, 1980-1992 were received in 1996, and comprise 3 linear feet in volume. The files are alphabetically arranged. As with previous accessions, this series includes information on personnel concerns and faculty and staff retirement and tenure procedures. There is also general information on the Graduate Employees Organization.
    - Appointment Procedures, 1980-1991 (Box 24)
    - Business and Finance Seminar, 1989 (Box 24)
    - Career Development, 1987-1989 (Box 24)
    - Career Ladders, 1986 (Box 24)
    - Compensation
      - 1981-1984 (Box 24)
      - 1982-1985 (Box 24)
      - 1986-1994 (Box 24)
    - Director Search, 1988-1989 (Box 31)
      [PR RESTRICTED until July 1 2019 ]
    - Diversity Task Force
      - 1990-1991 (Box 24)
      - 1992, 2 folders (Box 24)
      - 1993 (Box 24)
    - Early Retirement
      - 1980-1981 (Box 24)
      - 1982-1983 (Box 24)
      - 1984-1985 (Box 24)
      - 1986-1990 (Box 24)
    - Faculty Career Renewal Retreat, 1983 (Box 24)
    - Faculty Retirement Survey, 1987 (Box 24)
    - Family Care Resources Program, 1990-1994; 4 folders (Box 24)
    - Federal Income Tax
      - Issues and Benefits, 1983-1984 (Box 25)
      - Reform, 1980-1985 (Box 25)
    - Form "G" (re: history), 1976 (Box 25)
    - Graduate Employees Organization
      - General
        - 1981 (Box 25)
        - 1986 (Box 25)
        - 1987 (Box 25)
        - 1990-1992 (Box 25)
        - 1993 (Box 25)
      - Contract, 1993 (Box 25)
      - Negotiations, 1989/90; 2 folders (Box 25)
    - Grievance Activity by Contract, 1977-1982 (Box 25)
    - Jobnet
      - 1988 (Box 25)
      - 1989-1991 (Box 25)
      - 1992-1993 (Box 25)
      - 1994 (Box 25)
    - M-Quality, 1992-1994 (Box 25)
    - Reduction-In-Force Policy (RIF) Recommendations Committee
      - 1973-1988 (Box 25)
      - 1991-1992 (Box 25)
    - Sexual Harassment, 1980-1983; 3 folders (Box 27)
    - Statistical Reports: Personnel Head counts and Union Deductions, 1960-1970; 2 volumes (Box 26)
    - Tenure
      - Consideration, Chronology of, 1974-1982; 2 folders (Box 26)
      - Hefner Deliberations, 1980-1983; 13 folders (Box 27)
    - Tuition Waiver and Tax Withholding
      - 1980-1983 (Box 26)
      - 1984, 2 folders (Box 26)
      - 1985-1987 (Box 26)
      - 1988-1989, 2 folders (Box 26)
  - 1970-1994
    The Administrative Files, 1970-1994, are arranged alphabetically by topic or office name. Received in 1997, this subseries overlaps with the previously received administrative files series. Many of these files derive from offices within the Personnel Department, and consist primarily of monthly reports or reports and memos on specific subjects. Informative summary material on personnel activities can be found in the "Audits and Reviews," "Personnel Office--Reorganization," and "Personnel Office--Long Range Planning" files.
    - Administrative Services Personnel Office (ASPO) (Box 28)
      - Monthly Reports, 1987-1991 (Box 28)
      - Minutes and Correspondence, 1987-1992 (Box 28)
      - Salary Program and Merit Increases, 1988-1990 (Box 28)
    - Audits and Reviews
      - 1979, 1986; 1990; 1992 (Box 28)
      - 1987, 2 folders (Box 28)
    - Bargaining and Grievance Review Teams, 1991-1992 (Box 28)
    - Budget, 1988-1990 (Box 28)
    - Compensation Task Force, 1987-1989 (Box 28)
    - Correspondence, 1978-1991 (Box 28)
    - Dearborn Campus, 1985; 1992 (Box 28)
    - Employment Office, 1989-1991 (Box 28)
    - Faculty and Staff Assistance Program (see Personnel Support and Development Program) (Box 28)
    - Faculty and Staff Records Office, 1977-1990; 3 folders (Box 28)
    - Faculty and Staff Statistics Office, 1989-1991 (Box 28)
    - Faculty Personnel Policy (Review ), 1980-1985; 1986 (Box 28)
    - Family Care Resources Program (see Personnel Support and Development Program) (Box 28)
    - Flint Campus, 1986-1992 (Box 28)
    - Forms Revision, 1980-1983 (Box 28)
    - Human Resource Development (see Personnel Support and Development Program) (Box 28)
    - Medical Campus Human Resources
      - Attrition Management Task Force, 1991; 2 folders (Box 28)
      - Memos and Correspondence, 1987-1992; 3 folders (Box 28)
      - Nurse Recruitment Plan Analysis, 1990 (Box 28)
      - Supervisor Training, 1990 (Box 28)
      - University Hospital Personnel Services Review, 1970-1973; 2 folders (Box 28)
    - Personnel Office
      - Activity Reports, 1989-1993 (Box 28)
      - Automation
        - 1982-1989, undated (Box 28)
        - 1993 (Box 28)
      - Mission Statements, 1985-1988 (Box 28)
      - Office Flow Chart, 1981 (Box 28)
      - Organizational Charts, 1983-1990 (Box 28)
      - Performance Plans and Reviews, 1986-1988 (Box 28)
      - Planning, 1985-1988 (Box 28)
      - Reorganization, 1979; 1986-1990 (Box 28)
      - Staff Meetings, 1992 (Box 28)
      - Staffing and Organization, 1970-1979; undated (Box 28)
    - Personnel Data Systems
      - Appointment Subsystem, 1974 (Box 28)
      - Personnel Information Systems, 1971 (Box 28)
      - Reporting, 1974-1977 (Box 28)
      - Statistical Reporting, 1975-1978 (Box 28)
      - Task Force, 1973-1974 (Box 29)
    - Personnel Policy Group, 1986; 1992-1993 (Box 29)
    - Personnel Services Survey, 1986 (Box 29)
    - Personnel Support and Development
      - Reports and Correspondence, 1986-1994; 3 folders (Box 29)
      - Monthly Reports, 1987-1991; 2 folders (Box 29)
    - Professional/Administrative Positions, Ungraded, 1975-1985; undated; 2 folders (Box 29)
    - Salary Distribution, 1989 (Box 29)
    - Schools, Colleges, Institutes and Libraries (SCIL), 1989-1992; 3 folders (Box 29)
    - Staff Classifications
      - 1970 (Box 29)
      - undated (Box 29)
    - Staff Member Councils, 1971-1972 (Box 29)
    - Thiry, James, undated (Box 29)
  - 1963-1994
    The Administrative Files, 1963-1994 are arranged alphabetically by topic or office name and cover similar date spans to the previously received administrative files. The majority of the open files relate to the business operations and organizational planning of the Office of Human Resources and Affirmative Action.
    - Administrative Services-Davidson Institute, 1992 (Box 30)
    - Budget Reduction, 1979-1981 (Box 30)
    - Budgets
      - 1980-1992, 4 folders (Box 30)
      - Salaries, 1980-1991; 2 folders (Box 30)
    - Chemical Engineering Pilot Project, 1992 (Box 31)
      [PR RESTRICTED until July 1 2022 ]
    - Department Reorganization, 1980; 3 folders (Box 30)
    - Effort Reporting OMB A-21, 1963-1993 (Box 30)
    - Gamble, Dan, 1987-1992 (Box 31)
    - Human Resources Strategic Plan, 1991-1992 (Box 30)
    - Malinoski, Bernadette, 1980-1987 (Box 31)
    - Mediation
      - 1990-1994 (Box 31)
        [PR RESTRICTED until July 1 2024 ]
      - College of Engineering, 3 folders (Box 31)
      - Law School, 1990-1991 (Box 31)
        [PR RESTRICTED until July 1 2021 ]
      - Michigan Sea Grant, 1992-1993 (Box 31)
        [PR RESTRICTED until July 1 2023 ]
      - Museum of Art, 1991-1993; 2 folders (Box 31)
      - Office of Academic Multicultural Initiatives, 1993 (Box 31)
      - University Press, 1993 (Box 30)
    - Office of Administration Systems Supervisory Group, 1986-1990; 2 folders (Box 30)
    - Personnel Audit-Center for Research on Learning and Teaching, 1991-1994 (Box 31)
    - Personnel Evaluations, 1988-1990; 3 folders (Box 31)
    - Provost's Administrative Group, 1990-1993 (Box 30)
    - Provost's Advisory Committee on University Budgets, 1992-1993 (Box 30)
    - Service Delivery Project, 1990-1991 (Box 30)
    - Tenure, 1987-1991 (Box 30)
    - Transition Activity
      - Registrar's Office, 1993 (Box 31)
      - School of Social Work, 1993 (Box 30)
    - Unemployment Compensation, 1981-1994; 2 folders (Box 31)
    - University Promotion Appointment Guidelines, 1995/96-1996/97 (Box 30)
  - 1971-1994
    The Administrative Files, 1971-1994 (2 linear feet) subseries was received in the 2005 accession. As is the case with the other Administrative File series, the files are arranged alphabetically by topic or office name. The dates also overlap with previous Administrative Files subseries.
    - Child Care Task Force, 1990s (Box 32)
    - Faculty Compensation Reports, 1972; 1982; undated (Box 32)
    - Hayes Reports
      - Development of Uniform Salary Program, November 1971 (Box 32)
      - Summary of Responses from Interviews, February 1972 (Box 32)
      - Evaluation Committee #8, May 1972 (Box 32)
      - Proposed Salary Requirements for Research Staff, June 1972 (Box 32)
      - Proposed Approach to Salary Compensation for Research Staff, June 1972 (Box 32)
      - Proposed Approach to Salary Compensation for Research Staff (Non-student, Non-instructional), June 1972 (Box 32)
      - Evaluation Committee #1, June 1972 (Box 32)
      - Development of a Uniform Salary Program for Professional and Administrative Employees, September 1972 (Box 32)
      - Development of a Uniform Salary Program for Professional and Administrative Employees, Appendices, September 1972 (Box 32)
      - Review of Point Count Job Evaluation System, May 1973 (Box 32)
      - Survey of Compensation Levels Summary Report, December 1976 (Box 32)
      - Pay Report, April 1994 (Box 32)
    - HRAA Initiatives, 4 folders (Box 32)
    - Immigration Task Force, 3 folders (Box 33)
    - MERC, 2 folders (Box 33)
    - Michigan Mandate, drafts and correspondence (Box 33)
    - P and A Study Steering Committee, 1971-1973 (Box 33)
    - Rehired U of M Retirees (Box 33)
    - Retirement
      - Impact of Legal Changes, 1991 (Box 33)
      - Future Projections (Box 33)
    - Sabbatical Leave Reports (Box 33)
    - Salary Equity Study, 1989 (Box 33)
    - Staff Enhancement Task Team, 1987; 2 folders (Box 33)
    - Task Force on Retirement, 1993 (Box 33)
    - Uniform Salary Program Study, 2 folders
- Labor Relations
  The Labor Relations series is a rich source of information concerning the numerous unions on campus, their attempts to organize employees, and their demands on behalf of members. The series also documents the reactions and tactics of the Personnel Department staff and other university administrators. The subseries "History of Labor Relations at the University of Michigan" records the university's official stance towards unions from the late 1930s to the early 1970s, with emphasis on the 1960s. Within this subseries, The "Regents' Meetings Personnel Policies, 1937-1967" file is a useful summary, excerpting from the minutes of the board those decisions which affected labor relations or personnel policy. This subseries also documents the administration's reaction to the Hutchinson Act of 1965, and the subsequent upswing in union activity.
  The rest of the series is arranged alphabetically, and consists of files which correspond to specific unions, or specific groups of employees and their attempts to organize. Of special interest is the file relating to the Student Employees' Association and the file entitled "Faculty Unions". Activities of the Association of Federal, State, County, and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), Local 1583, are well documented for the years 1958 to 1968, especially 1958 to 1961. The union made demands on behalf of its entire membership, as well as on behalf of individual employees with specific grievances. The Personnel Office also collected fliers and news clippings related to this union. Relations with the Building Service Employees' International Union (BSEIU), Local 378 are documented from 1966 to 1968. However, files covering the years 1949 to 1966 were destroyed in 1968. In 1970, the Teamster's Union challenged AFSCME for right to represent service and maintenance employees, and the file "Teamsters' Organizing Drive" documents this event.
  - Association of Federal, State, County, and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), Local 1583 (Box 29)
  - Fliers and Clippings, 1958-1970; 7 folders (Box 29)
  - Minutes and Correspondence
    - 1958-1959 (Box 29)
    - 1960, 2 folders (Box 29)
    - 1961, 2 folders (Box 29)
    - 1962 (Box 29)
    - 1963-1966 (Box 29)
    - 1967 (Box 29)
    - 1968 (Box 29)
  - Building Service Employees' International Union (BSEIU), Local 378, 1966-1968 (Box 29)
  - Clerical/Technical Unions, 1974; 1981-1989 (Box 29)
  - Faculty Unions, 1971-1992; 2 folders (Box 29)
  - Firefighters, 1972 (Box 29)
  - History of Labor Relations at University of Michigan
    - Regents' Meetings Personnel Policies, 1937-1967 (Box 29)
    - General
      - 1940, 1950; 1960-1966 (Box 29)
      - 1967-1973, undated
        - Labor Relations (cont.) (Box 29)
    - Labor Relations Code, 1945-1950 (Box 30)
    - Labor Petitions, 1965-1967 (Box 30)
    - News Clippings, 1965-1967 (Box 30)
    - Hutchinson Act, 1966-1967; undated (Box 30)